Contact

0724631091 (Mobile) munenejoypatience@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/joypatiencemunene (LinkedIn) mokosoko.com/ (Company)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Customer Service Social Media

Publications

How Afghanistan's Economy will be affected by the Taliban's Rule

A Step By Step Guide on How To Deal With Angry Customers.

Joypatience Munene

Founder Unda Africa & Co-Founder MokoSoko Nyali, Mombasa, Kenya

Summary

JoyPatience is a friendly and professional business developer and community organizer with strong administrative skills, has experience in resolving escalated customer complaints, and strong interpersonal skills are proven through client satisfaction. Seeks to expand career growth in a senior position as an administration officer. She has worked with well-known top brands across diverse industries in Nairobi such as East African Breweries Limited, FUNDIS APP, and CLOUD9XP.

She has acquired valuable skills and connections within the East African Business Community and is currently interested in taking on new brands as a full-time or part-time evangelist, publicist, or market influencer.

She was the recent online marketing community manager at FUNDIS a role that has seen her coordinate publicity efforts in more than 15 Technical Vocational Training Institutions where FUNDIS has many evangelists.

She is currently working with Blockybits creative studio as a business developer and creative studio manager as her experience in both roles precede her.

Experience

Unda Africa Founder Unda Africa March 2022 - Present (7 months) Kenya & Rwanda

MokoSoko COO & Co-Founder March 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months) **Blockybits**

3 years 1 month

Creative Studio Manager

June 2019 - June 2022 (3 years 1 month)

Nairobi, Kenya

A team of multidisciplinary digital experts focused on visual brand identity, web, mobile app, and software development. In her capability as a creative manager, she has the following roles:-

Liaise with Talent & Creative Resource Management on the hiring & managing freelance talent.

Manage project scopes, timelines & budgets for studio projects.

Communicate & manage project expectations with creative departments.

Help grow & drive the efficiency of the department through training & technology.

Recommend measures to improve work process methods,

equipment performance, and quality of products.

Conduct daily evaluation of workload balance and assignments.

Community Engagement Lead January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months)

FUNDIS APP

Online Marketing Coordinator

November 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Nairobi, Mandera Road Kileleshwa

FUNDIS is skilled crafts, trades and repairs platform that links users with college

educated, competent, vetted and reliable specialists in Kenya. It's a linkedin for the linked

out in the world's developing economies.

To put her administrative and coordination skills to work, she is periodically tasked with

keeping the FUNDIS community of volunteers and brand evangelists in various universities

and Technical Vocational training institutions/ colleges vibrant and fruitful

Cloud9xp

Business developer

February 2019 - June 2019 (5 months)

Nairobi, Kenya

An online retailer and booking service for leisure experiences. The company believes that everyone deserves to have fun, feel good and be happy. It focuses on amplifying happiness to its clients. In her role she was involved in identifying new business opportunities, building, maintaining successful relationships with prospects & existing clients, collaborating with executives on business strategy to determine objectives, and Evaluating business performance.

CYNTEQ LTD

Kenya

Junior Supervisor June 2017 - August 2017 (3 months)

CYNTEQ TECHNOLOGIES is a Preeminent Information technology company with

key specialties in brands design, brands formation, activation and online visibility

(Spans through brandworks, web and mobile apps).

JoyPatience had the privilege to be a junior supervisor acting as a link between the various

company departments and reporting to the managing director. In her capacity as

the junior supervisor she had the following roles:

- a) Company record keeping.
- b) Managing clients social media accounts
- c) Preparing written submissions to clients.
- d) Was in charge of day to day secretarial duties (to the management of the company)
- e) Identifying and proactively resolving problems areas internally and with the clients.
- f) Conducting team performance analysis and reporting the same to the management
- g) Maintaining correspondence with clients

Trueblaq
Brand Ambassador
January 2016 - December 2016 (1 year)

True Blaq is an experiential marketing and event company/agency based in Nairobi

that helps to strengthen brands and their visibility.

As a brand Ambassador she took on different administrative, sales and marketing

roles consequently gaining top notch organizing and planning skills. JoyPatience had the following key roles:

- 1. Increasing awareness of EABL brands in Nairobi and her environs
- 2. Responsible for generating sales opportunities in multiple regions.
- 3. Customer relationship management.
- 4. Responsible for conducting market analysis for brand positioning
- 5. Building customer preference

Deenote Technologies Limited Business Development Intern January 2016 - December 2016 (1 year) Nairobi, Kenya

NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT Data Transcriber

April 2015 - August 2015 (5 months)

Nairobi

National Council for Population and Development is the governmental sector which

deals with improvement of the standards of living and quality of life of the people, full integration of population concerns into the development process.

While working for the company, she had the following responsibilities:

- a) Collected Data, conducted analysis
- b) Transcribed data from audio recordings to both typed and handwritten.
- c) Translated recordings from local dialect to English and swahili without distortion of information.

Education

Kenyatta University

Bachelor's degree, Public Policy and Administration (2014 - 2018)